# CHRISTOPHER HOSKEN

99/474 Soi 13, San Sai Noi, San Sai, Chiang Mai, TH Mobile: (086)-761-8606 | hoskenchristopher@gmail.com

### Summary

A high-school student with over seven years of experience in animation. I use tools such as Blender, Houdini, Nuke, and DaVinci Resolve, alongside leadership skills to direct short films. I pride myself on being an open and excited artist, and I like to think my ability to appreciate new ideas has played a large part in how I associate with and understand others.

#### Education

Chiang Mai International School 2010-Current

Chiang Mai, TH GPA: Unweighted: 3.82

SAT: 1400

Relevant Coursework: AP Physics 1 & 2, AP Computer Science, AP 2D Art & Design, AP Calculus BC

## Experience

### **Director, BOAP Studios**

September 2020 - April 2021

After finishing our first animation at BOAP Studios, I was given the chance to write and direct another short film. I also worked with the team to create assets and program our own production tools. It was during this time that I decided to pursue becoming a technical artist.

#### **Producer, BOAP Studios**

March 2019 - September 2020

During my first year and a half at BOAP Studios, I took a hands-on producer role. I helped with writing, modeling, and animation alongside managing the team. Through this, I learned the foundations of how a studio operates, and how to deal with conflicts and challenges that arise.

#### Awards / Honors

"Fallout Shopping" Official Selection Award Beyond Animation Festival (2022)

Academic Excellence Award Chiang Mai International School (2019-2022)

**AP® Scholar with Honor** Chiang Mai International School (2022)

Skills

Computer Blender | Houdini | Nuke | DaVinci Resolve | Visual Studio | Figma

**Programming** Python | Java | C++ | Kotlin | HTML | CSS | Javascript

Film Scriptwriting | Storyboarding | Concept Art | Visual language

## **Additional Skills**

French Limited proficiency

Google Suite Experienced in all aspects

**Business** Understanding of organizational structures and marketing strategies

**Lead teams** in a broad variety of situations